<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?mso-application progid="Excel.Sheet"?>
<Workbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet"
 xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office"
 xmlns:x="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel"
 xmlns:ss="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet"
 xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40">
 <DocumentProperties xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office">
  <Author>Shariq Mian</Author>
  <LastAuthor>Shariq Mian</LastAuthor>
  <Created>2021-10-10T23:35:19Z</Created>
  <LastSaved>2021-10-10T23:36:22Z</LastSaved>
  <Version>16.00</Version>
 </DocumentProperties>
 <OfficeDocumentSettings xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office">
  <AllowPNG/>
 </OfficeDocumentSettings>
 <ExcelWorkbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel">
  <WindowHeight>11715</WindowHeight>
  <WindowWidth>25200</WindowWidth>
  <WindowTopX>32767</WindowTopX>
  <WindowTopY>32767</WindowTopY>
  <ProtectStructure>False</ProtectStructure>
  <ProtectWindows>False</ProtectWindows>
 </ExcelWorkbook>
 <Styles>
  <Style ss:ID="Default" ss:Name="Normal">
   <Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
   <Borders/>
   <Font ss:FontName="Calibri" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Size="11" ss:Color="#000000"/>
   <Interior/>
   <NumberFormat/>
   <Protection/>
  </Style>
  <Style ss:ID="s68">
   <NumberFormat ss:Format="0"/>
  </Style>
 </Styles>
 <Worksheet ss:Name="booklist">
  <Table ss:ExpandedColumnCount="10" ss:ExpandedRowCount="8" x:FullColumns="1"
   x:FullRows="1" ss:DefaultRowHeight="15">
   <Column ss:Index="3" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="84"/>
   <Column ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="70.5"/>
   <Column ss:Index="6" ss:StyleID="s68" ss:Width="78"/>
   <Column ss:Index="8" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="60"/>
   <Column ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="57.75"/>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">book_title</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">book_authors</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">book_desc</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">book_edition</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">book_format</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">book_isbn</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">book_pages</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">book_rating</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">book_rating_count</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">genres</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Hunger Games</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Suzanne Collins</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Winning will make you famous. Losing means certain death.The nation of Panem, formed from a post-apocalyptic North America, is a country that consists of a wealthy Capitol region surrounded by 12 poorer districts. Early in its history, a rebellion led by a 13th district against the Capitol resulted in its destruction and the creation of an annual televised event known as the Hunger Games. In punishment, and as a reminder of the power and grace of the Capitol, each district must yield one boy and one girl between the ages of 12 and 18 through a lottery system to participate in the games. The 'tributes' are chosen during the annual Reaping and are forced to fight to the death, leaving only one survivor to claim victory.When 16-year-old Katniss's young sister, Prim, is selected as District 12's female representative, Katniss volunteers to take her place. She and her male counterpart Peeta, are pitted against bigger, stronger representatives, some of whom have trained for this their whole lives. , she sees it as a death sentence. But Katniss has been close to death before. For her, survival is second nature.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="5"><Data ss:Type="String">Hardcover</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">9780440000000</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">374 pages</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4.33</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">5519135</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Young Adult|Fiction|Science Fiction|Dystopia|Fantasy|Science Fiction</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">J.K. Rowling|Mary GrandPré</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">There is a door at the end of a silent corridor. And it’s haunting Harry Pottter’s dreams. Why else would he be waking in the middle of the night, screaming in terror?Harry has a lot on his mind for this, his fifth year at Hogwarts: a Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher with a personality like poisoned honey; a big surprise on the Gryffindor Quidditch team; and the looming terror of the Ordinary Wizarding Level exams. But all these things pale next to the growing threat of He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named&#45;&#45;-a threat that neither the magical government nor the authorities at Hogwarts can stop.As the grasp of darkness tightens, Harry must discover the true depth and strength of his friends, the importance of boundless loyalty, and the shocking price of unbearable sacrifice.His fate depends on them alll.(back cover)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">US Edition</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Paperback</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">9780440000000</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">870 pages</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4.4800000000000004</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2041594</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Fantasy|Young Adult|Fiction</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">To Kill a Mockingbird</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Harper Lee</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The unforgettable novel of a childhood in a sleepy Southern town and the crisis of conscience that rocked it, To Kill A Mockingbird became both an instant bestseller and a critical success when it was first published in 1960. It went on to win the Pulitzer Prize in 1961 and was later made into an Academy Award-winning film, also a classic.Compassionate, dramatic, and deeply moving, To Kill A Mockingbird takes readers to the roots of human behavior - to innocence and experience, kindness and cruelty, love and hatred, humor and pathos. Now with over 18 million copies in print and translated into forty languages, this regional story by a young Alabama woman claims universal appeal. Harper Lee always considered her book to be a simple love story. Today it is regarded as a masterpiece of American literature.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">50th Anniversary</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Paperback</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">9780060000000</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">324 pages</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4.2699999999999996</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3745197</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Classics|Fiction|Historical|Historical Fiction|Academic|School</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Twilight</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Stephenie Meyer</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">About three things I was absolutely positive.First, Edward was a vampire.Second, there was a part of him—and I didn't know how dominant that part might be—that thirsted for my blood.And third, I was unconditionally and irrevocably in love with him.In the first book of the Twilight Saga, internationally bestselling author Stephenie Meyer introduces Bella Swan and Edward Cullen, a pair of star-crossed lovers whose forbidden relationship ripens against the backdrop of small-town suspicion and a mysterious coven of vampires. This is a love story with bite.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="5"><Data ss:Type="String">Paperback</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">9780320000000</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">498 pages</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.58</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4281268</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Young Adult|Fantasy|Romance|Paranormal|Vampires|Fiction|Fantasy|Paranormal</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Book Thief</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Markus Zusak</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Trying to make sense of the horrors of World War II, Death relates the story of Liesel&#45;-a young German girl whose book-stealing and story-telling talents help sustain her family and the Jewish man they are hiding, as well as their neighbors.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">First American Edition (US / CAN)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Hardcover</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">9780380000000</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">552 pages</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4.3600000000000003</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1485632</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Historical|Historical Fiction|Fiction|Young Adult</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Chronicles of Narnia</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">C.S. Lewis|Pauline Baynes</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Journeys to the end of the world, fantastic creatures, and epic battles between good and evil—what more could any reader ask for in one book? The book that has it all is The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, written in 1949 by Clive Staples Lewis. But Lewis did not stop there. Six more books followed, and together they became known as The Chronicles of Narnia.For the past fifty years, The Chronicles of Narnia have transcended the fantasy genre to become part of the canon of classic literature. Each of the seven books is a masterpiece, drawing the reader into a land where magic meets reality, and the result is a fictional world whose scope has fascinated generations.This edition presents all seven books—unabridged—in one impressive volume. The books are presented here in chronlogical order, each chapter graced with an illustration by the original artist, Pauline Baynes. Deceptively simple and direct, The Chronicles of Narnia continue to captivate fans with adventures, characters, and truths that speak to readers of all ages, even fifty years after they were first published.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Reissue Edition</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Paperback</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">9780070000000</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">767 pages</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4.25</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">437829</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Fantasy|Classics|Fiction|Young Adult|Childrens</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Gone with the Wind</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Margaret Mitchell</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Gone with the Wind is a novel written by Margaret Mitchell, first published in 1936. The story is set in Clayton County, Georgia, and Atlanta during the American Civil War and Reconstruction era. It depicts the struggles of young Scarlett O'Hara, the daughter of a well-to-do plantation owner, who must use every means at her disposal to claw her way out of the poverty she finds herself in after Sherman's March to the Sea. A historical novel, the story is a Bildungsroman or coming-of-age story, with the title taken from a poem written by Ernest Dowson.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="5"><Data ss:Type="String">Paperback</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">9780450000000</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1037 pages</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4.29</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">969181</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Classics|Historical|Historical Fiction|Fiction|Romance|Historical</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
  </Table>
  <WorksheetOptions xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel">
   <PageSetup>
    <Header x:Margin="0.3"/>
    <Footer x:Margin="0.3"/>
    <PageMargins x:Bottom="0.75" x:Left="0.7" x:Right="0.7" x:Top="0.75"/>
   </PageSetup>
   <Print>
    <ValidPrinterInfo/>
    <HorizontalResolution>600</HorizontalResolution>
    <VerticalResolution>600</VerticalResolution>
   </Print>
   <Selected/>
   <Panes>
    <Pane>
     <Number>3</Number>
     <ActiveRow>19</ActiveRow>
     <ActiveCol>10</ActiveCol>
    </Pane>
   </Panes>
   <ProtectObjects>False</ProtectObjects>
   <ProtectScenarios>False</ProtectScenarios>
  </WorksheetOptions>
 </Worksheet>
</Workbook>
